Aleksandar Bakraceski



bakraceskia@gmail.com



+38972565426



linkedin.com/in/aleksandar-bakraceski-393524ab

Summary

My few years of experience as a Front End Developer has honed my CSS3, HTML5, JS, Polymer.js, Vue.js React.js skills, as well as my knowledge of mobile and responsive design. My professional experience includes bringing the wireframes of the UX designer to life through HTML5 and CSS3, as well as collaborating with Back End Developers to create a stellar finished product. I think my skills and experience makes me a great fit for your company.

Here are some of my most relevant qualifications and accomplishments:

Good experience as a Front End Developer

Crafted various website features using HTML5 CSS3 ,JavaScript, Polymerjs and Vuejs.

Developed and Implemented project scope and timelines based on the design-develop-deploy process Collaborated with UX designers and Back End Developers and ensured coherence between all parties Tested feature prototypes for bugs and user experience

skype: bakracheski123

email: bakraceskia@gmail.com

Experience

Frontend Developer

Heart for Health ICT

Jul 2020 - Present (6 months +)

Working as a Frontend developer using Vue.js as a main JS Framework.

Senior Frontend Developer

qBit Solutions

Sep 2018 - Jun 2020 (1 year 10 months)

Developing web and mobile blockchain applications using Vue.js, React, Javascript, HTML, CSS.

Working on a few blockchain projects for trading (buy/sell) cryptocurrencies,log in/ log out, handle your personal wallet, follow your transactions, make it responsive and so many other features.

Team Lead

qBit Solutions

Jan 2019 - Jan 2020 (1 year 1 month)

Frontend Developer

Blueshift

Oct 2016 - Sep 2018 (2 years)

Programming 3D video games and web APPs using Javascript, Jquery, HTML, CSS, Polymer.js, Three.js

- Working on 3D Games project using Three.js,
- Developing platform for creating CVs (create CV, update, delete and features for exporting in choosen template in PDF/Word),
- Also project for transport company (creating caterogies of vehicles, add, edit and delete vehicles) to know and follow all infos about each vehicle

Main task in role:

Develop and redesign UIs

Develop optimized web applications with maximum speed and scalability

Bug fixing

Oracle PL-SQL Programming

Spd computing

Aug 2016 - Sep 2016 (2 months)

Angular.js developer

ATS Macedonia

Jun 2016 - Jul 2016 (2 months)

Javascript, HTML, CSS, Angular.js (Nhibernate, automapper, dependency injection, data binding)

Education

I○ Faculty of Computer Science and Engineering - Skopje

Bachelor's Degree, Computer science and engineering 2013 - 2018

SUGS "Georgi Dimitrov"

High School 2009 - 2013

Skills

HTML • JavaScript • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • Computer Science • Software Development • Algorithms • Programming • Responsive Web Design • Front-end Development • Web Applications